I need us to stop saying violations of international law.
I even heard myself say that the other day and I was like, girl, what are you talking about?
There is no such thing as international law. There has been imperial control.
The United Nations are not a body that enforces any concept of the international law unless it is going to be in the best interests of the central banks, the Vatican, etc.
So when I hear folks like Jeffrey Sachs address the United Nations and say, you know, this is a violation of international law, it's starting to get my goat or my horses because there has never been international law.
If we want to talk about violations of international law, how can we not talk about the amount of extrajudicial killings that have been done by the United States, by the European nations?
The amount of coups, of infiltration of elections, the stealing of resources.
Hello, Palestine has been in the situation it's in since 1945.
The United Nations was formed right around that time, post-World War II.
The United Nations was not formed to be a body to stop the world from going to war again.
The United Nations was a body created by the United States to control the world and prevent it from going to war against the United States, the new colonizer.
Until these realities are espoused loudly, particularly in these spaces like the United Nations, by the individuals who represent nations like the United States, we are just talking out of our necks.
There has never been international law.
There has been international control.
No, the laws were not decided upon by all of the bodies.
And the fact that only one body can veto a unilateral decision agreed upon by everybody else lets you know.
Let's start calling it what it is.
It took me only two years of paying attention to understand that.
So I don't know why people who have dedicated their lives to this are still living in ideological nonsense.
It is useless.